and no one's passing the ball to me anymore
oh that poor kid look at number two over there everyone on his team is ignoring him that's not
nice they're making the right call enough is enough Aoi you know what I feel better
you really got me a tryouts man I couldn't stop obsessing about that one play thinking what I
could have done differently now I see it was a total fluke and you you're no one
sorry maybe you don't remember me I'm Asari Asari marks June
Asari marks June.
Never seen anyone so obsessed with ball retention.
And he works hard. Owns his tactics all year round.
Damn bastard! He'll regret that!
Hey guys! Move up!
I can't let the game end like this!
If they don't like it, they can suck it!
Yuma! Over here!
We don't need you, Ashito!
Get that through your head!
Then there's that one.
He's on a totally different level than everyone else.
Yuma.
Kamiyama!
Yuma! What are you doing?
The goal's back in the other direction!
Why are you dribbling the wrong way all of the sudden?
Strategy.
He's trying to draw out one of the other team's defenders.
Kuruda!
I don't think so.
Cross field pass.
Straight to Kuruda.
Right, Yuma?
Togashi!
What the heck's he doing?
Hey guys! Move up!
So you can follow instructions, huh?
Looks like you might be more than just a meathead.
To Togashi!
Barking instructions.
That's it.
That's the one crucial difference between him and Ashito Ali.
Do you see it?
It's the key to mastering individual tactics. You have to be able to put into words what you do and make it your own. When you do, you can give precise instructions to those around you.
Yuma's good. He's been extraordinary ever since he was on the junior youth team. Even though Ashito scored earlier, Yuma was the one who made it possible.
He sensed Aoi's nonverbal intentions and kept the ball near the goal. He has the awareness and the skills to utilize those around him. In fact, he's the ideal forward for Asperion.
Because I stayed here, Asuri wasn't able to provide cover. Stand here and do nothing. That was the only role they assigned me.
This isn't the first time no one's wanted to pass to me.
At a soccer club in Ehime, they said I was a selfish player.
Everyone hated me.
That was straight up bullying. They wouldn't let me play at all.
But this feels totally different.
It was strategy. They didn't need me to make that goal.
They ignored me so that they could score. I guess I can't blame them.
But it still hurts, being told to just stand there.
Meaning when anyone looks at me, all they see is dead weight.
That's it. Time's up. Good job, everyone. As for who made the A-team...
Yuma Motoki? That's it.
Damn it!
I was so useless, no one would give me the ball.
I scored a goal for us, but it didn't make a difference.
Why?
I don't get it. What the hell was the frickin' problem?
How am I supposed to know what I did wrong if they don't tell me?
Damn it!
Is that you, Owie?
Go on, Cootie. I'll catch up with you later.
Haven't seen you since the tryouts. Looks like you made the cut, huh? Congrats.
Go home.
It's sad to see such a lack of talent.
I hope that face doesn't mean you're surprised to see me.
I'm your senior. Of course I'm here.
I was in the clubhouse on the second floor, with Fukuda and some other seniors.
We had a great view of you on the field from up there. Very entertaining.
Is there something you want?
Can't say I'm surprised at how little you've changed since the tryouts.
Seriously, though. How the hell did you get them to sign you?
Can't be much of a player if your teammates are going out of their way to ignore you.
What's done is done. They put you on the team. Three years of kicking a ball in a corner.
That's the only thing you're good for. So I hope you enjoy it, dumbass.
You're wrong. You don't know me. I'll crawl out of this and keep getting better. Just you wait.
You've got some dumb parents, too. That's a lot of money to waste on a defunct kid.
They must really want that signing bonus from your first pro contract or something, huh?
Every year, desperate soccer moms push their sweet, talentless sons onto the youth team.
Don't even go there. Don't talk about my family. They have nothing to do with this.
Sure they do. They have everything to do with it. They're paying for you to be here.
I'm curious. Did you think things would magically work out when you joined?
Did you expect someone to hold your hand and teach you how to play?
Is that how you figured you'd step up to our level?
Maybe. Maybe he's right about me.
I thought I was prepared, but maybe I wasn't committed enough.
I swear, we get more and more softies like you on the youth team every year.
What a joke. Such a waste.
If that's true, if I really didn't give it my all before coming here, the way the others did, then what can I do to fix it?
I think a good strategy would be... Huh?
Tell me! I want to fix it. Where do I start?
Well, come on. You know what I'm talking about. Tell me what I'm lacking. I'll do anything.
I'm begging you! Help me! Teach me how to play soccer! Your way!
Your way!
Hi, Hana.
What's up?
I think that it's starting to make sense. I know why you like him. That player called Ashito Aoi.
He plays like him. It's similar. Their styles, I mean.
I know how you feel. At least, I...
So, are we hugging now?
Who is that? Hana?
Huh? Hey there, bro!
I didn't know you were still here.
Whoa, you're the Kaido electric girl. It all makes sense now. You're seeing her off. That's nice of you.
Weee... Kai?
Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai... Kai...
Kinda crazy?
I'm Enri Kaido. I haven't seen you in so long! Manager Fukura...
Uh!
Your leadership is always impeccable! And today was another example!
They should start calling you the Japanese Mourinho!
Mourinho, huh?
Great manager. But he didn't make a name for himself as a player, so...
it's not much of a compliment it was a joke i swear i was just messing with you i think that
it's starting to make sense i know why you like him that player called ashito ali
he plays like him
hana i want you to meet a special lady we've been thinking about getting married
well hello hana i'm kinio fukuda and this young man is her son tatsuya fukuda
it's nice knowing my mom found such a great guy for a partner
now i don't have to feel bad about going to spain to play soccer
you must love her very much of course i do she's the reason i'm living my dream right now
i i i love you
i remember the first time i saw my brother up close and i'll never forget his eyes
the expression behind them was just so calm and at the same time his confidence sparkled
feels like it was only days ago
what's up
will you please go talk to him
what is he doing out here
well he asked coach datte for advice
kill it kick it
simple it's the most basic of the basics and you don't even have that down you're starting
just please show me how to do it right
and so now here we are it's been like hours hasn't even taken a break yet
you know if there is one thing ashito's got it's grit
it's never been the way he plays the game that's similar
to me it's his eyes no matter how cornered he is that fire inside never burns out
as long as he holds on to that spark he could become a star player
i'm here for it i'm on this ride till the end
oh hey ashito goodness what have you been up to
hello shun i have something i'd like to ask you don't sound so formal what's up
how much did the youth team cost like to send me here for three years what are you even asking me
how much it costs do you mean in terms of money uh yeah what else i just realized that mom had never
told me oh well she's right here i can put her on and you can ask her yourself no it's cool i don't
have to talk to her what i can't yet look i haven't achieved anything so i just let her down
you've got some dumb parents too that's a lot of money to waste on a defunct kid
i need to know okay please shun ask mom how much it all costs so that i can focus on playing
come on it's real important
you heard him
okay you ready yeah go the monthly fees 6 000 yen housing's 5 000 a month as for meals your lunch and
dinner are free but you have to pay 300 for breakfast every day all together that's about
20 000 every month that's 240 000 a year plus the yearly expedition rate of 60 000 so grand total is
300 000 a year but you know at least it's cheaper than having to pay it back i promise club fees tuition
living expenses transportation all of it i'll have it within three years would you tell mom that
what do you mean within three years you're basically saying that
oh don't get too worked up about it okay
dude why are you letting the ball bounce up like that
we're supposed to be practicing passing but the ball stops every time it gets to you you're throwing
off the entire group's rhythm bro nagano no guy's still new why not try to go easy on him okay
come on this is some basic little league kindergarten crap here tida
i'm sorry man i wish i could tell you not to worry youth team's about survival we just don't have
time for somebody who can't keep up what's with the chatter get back to work gotta go meet you
you're out of line he's a first year i'm just being real i mean i had no choice dude has got no
basic skills and he thinks he can go pro it screams laziness to me you know i guess so what's the
matter
thing is i've seen him working i swear he practices alone after everyone's gone home for the day
every night at the dorm all by himself after seeing that i just
crap it just bounced back up again why can't i do it this sucks
it's been a whole week now i practice the same thing every single night and i'm still not getting
any better no way am i giving up though i'm gonna master it and soon i'll show him
this hurdle may slow me down but it won't stop me hey
ever heard of quality over quantity oh hey you guys what's going on word to the wise my man want
to get better quickly don't train solo we'll help you practice wait no what are you talking about i
couldn't ask you guys to do something like that just for me huh i think you got the wrong idea we came
out here to review our basics that's all it might look like we're helping but we're really just
showing off how much better we are than you you feel me ha now come on go time we're the tryout trio
right let's show them what we've got thanks you guys just you wait i'll be better than all of you in
no time sure you will idiot where's your stamina today you shouldn't be an exhausted mess this early
in practice i'm real sorry coach sounds like someone's practicing too much after our drill session
should never interfere with our regular training but regular training won't be enough i have to do
more than anyone else out here otherwise i can't close the gap that's between us if i don't do something
it'll just keep getting wider you know i got an interesting call today somebody's been leaving the
dorm at night and not making their way back until after lights out more than one somebody in fact
three apparently so tell me owie have you been stupid enough to ignore curfew for the sake of a little
extra practice time toga she you're always roommate so you would know has he been breaking dorm rules
and sneaking out at night beats me can't see a guy break rules if i'm asleep
it looks like you've been practicing a lot the kill it then kick it technique yeah
sorry i didn't see you there don't look so down little dude you're working your butt off
oh so anyway you're toga she's roomie right yeah so what maybe it's because he was scouted but
he's not like us guys who came up through junior youth he doesn't fit the mold big and rough
around the edges but he plays the game right he has the basics down for sure
why not look closer to home for help
what you want to take the night off well yeah coach stone face yelled at me earlier so i figure i should
lay low for at least a little while and besides i bet you guys could use some rest too right sure see
uh later
i don't want special treatment and i don't want them to get dragged down because of me
so going out alone huh you're working hard and i'm not going to complain about getting the room
all to myself but you're on edge man do you know what the dead giveaway is your eyes
there's a screw loose in your head or something you take things too far what you need is for somebody
to rein you in otherwise you'll burn yourself out in no time and your soccer career will be over
um yes sorry but i'm not sure what you're saying i'm saying that maybe you should take a break
well that's not happening then prepare for some epic burnout not happening either sure you're gonna be
just fine please check how stressed you look all right i'm impatient everybody else is so skilled
i feel like i'm falling further and further behind them and i hate that you're totally wrong about me
being stressed though i'm having fun seriously it's great i'm here to play with the best and be judged
by the best i have to go at it with everything i've got in me or else i'm gonna be left in the dust
it's something i've always wanted but never found before this is where i belong
like i said you gotta screw loose makes it interesting though i'll give you that
tonight you're practicing with me when we're done you'll know the real meaning of kill it then kick it
you're ready you're ready you're ready you
Next time on Awashi, a broader soccer.